# Tramaine Harper

**Recruiter/ Kohls - Corporate Office** 

Hutchins, TX 75141 curtistramaine@hotmail.com (214) 563-0578

Talent recruitment and acquisition professional with experience developing and executing recruiting plans within both agency and in-house settings. Customer Service specialist, with over 20 years of call center/ clerical roles.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

#### **Recruiter/ Kohls**

Corporate Office - Dallas, TX February 2016 to Present

Aggressively recruited well-qualified applicants from a variety of sources, including job boards, social media, and sourcing on Kohl's applicant tracking system resume database. Conducted comprehensive telephone screening interviews and overseeing the administration of pre-employment assessments. Conducted and oversaw the coordination of first and second interviews; extend employment offers according to established procedures. Managed the applicant flow through ICISMS ATS for assigned requisitions. Assisted with new hire orientation.

### **Senior Credit Card Account Manager**

Santander Consumer USA - Dallas, TX October 2011 to October 2015

Research customers account using company records and Internet resources that are made available. Conduct custom collections campaigns on each client that consist of emails, phone calls and standard mail correspondence. Also helping to develop collections methods that consistently lead to achieving or exceeding company financial goals. Work closely with team members to create ways to bring in revenue and find success as a group. Solve problems quickly and create resolutions that bring in revenue on a regular basis. Escalation calls coaching and development.

### **Technical Support Specialist**

Monitronics - Dallas, TX February 2005 to July 2011

Keep customers informed of progress during issue life cycle and make follow-up calls or communications in a timely manner. Assist team members and provide support and solutions to customer queries to meet company objectives. Maintain updated knowledge of company products and services to better provide customer support and service solutions.

#### Education

#### **Bachelor of Arts in Criminal Justice**

# Skills

MS OFFICE, ONBOARDING, SALES, SALES AND, TALENT ASSESSMENT

# Additional Information

Skills

PC & MS Office proficient

Strong organizational and management skills

Excellent interpersonal and communication skills

Outstanding skills in training new customer care representatives

Sales and support

Trainer
Talent Assessment & Acquisition
Placement & Onboarding
Offer Negotiations